David Braga Vieira

Software Developer

021 140 6539

bragav.david@gmail.com

david-braga

in _{David Braga V.}

davidbraga.netlify.app

ABOUT ME

I am a 39yo Brazilian who has been living in New Zealand for more than 9 years. I started coding 3y ago doing online courses at night and weekends while working during week-days.

Recently I have completed a Software Development Bootcamp with Dev Academy where I rapidly improved my skills and expanded my knowledge.

I am in love with Web Development and want to be part of New Zealand's Tech Industry Growth.

I am a team player, enthusiastic and a quick learner.

My previous experiences as a Tour Guide (back in Brazil), Hotel Receptionist and Abseiler gave me great interpersonal skills and the ability to work well under pressure. I enjoy working with challenges.

SKILLS

Teamplayer

Attention to detail

Enthusiastic

Self-Motivated

TECHNOLOGY

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Typescript

Node Js.

Testing (Jest)

GitHub

React

Redux

ExpressJs

EXPERIENCE

Home Office, Remote— Student

JAN 2022 - PRESENT

- Networking
- Working on personal projects
- Applying for first Developer job

Enspiral Dev Academy, Remote — Student

AUG 2021 - DEC 2021

- Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp
- 700+ hours coding
- Multiple projects in a team environment
- Agile principles replicating real life conditions

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

English

Spanish

CitySide Properties Ltd, Auckland — Height Technician/ Team leader

JUN 2017 - AUG 2021

- General building maintenance via abseil
- Liaise with clients
- Working in teams following safety standards
- Meeting deadlines for completion

Swiss Belsuites Victoria Park, Auckland — Hotel Receptionist

FEB 2017 - JUN 2017

- Greet and check- in/check- out of guests
- Liaise with GM and other departments
- Manage bookings and in-house guests requests
- Create bookings for new arrivals
- Night auditing

Black Sheep Backpackers, Queentown — *Front Desk*

DEC 2014 - DEC 2016

- Check-in and check-out of guests
- Make bookings
- Liaise with the Director and the Housekeeping team

EDUCATION

Enspiral Dev Academy, Auckland, NZ — Full Stack Web Development Certificate

AUG 2021 - DEC 2021

Crown Institute, Auckland, NZ — Travel and Tourism Diploma

FEB 2013 - JUN 2013

IESB - Higher Education Institute of Brasilia, Brasilia, BR —

Travel and Tourism Bachelor Degree

FEB 2000 - DEC 2004

REFERENCES

Available upon request.